(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.1",
"generated_at": "2026-08-02T01:57:04.635854",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.1-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
3D Birthday LIVE 2026 - THE ONE & ONLY -
[Title Card: Isaki Riona 3D Birthday LIVE 2026 - THE ONE & ONLY -]
Hey, everybody!
Today, I would like to introduce you...
...to the one, the only, entertainer!
Riona!
始まったショータイム 鳴り響く歓声
The showtime has begun, the cheers are ringing out!
Let's get it up, get it up, get it up
お邪魔が邪魔？心躍らせ Susie
Is trouble in the way? Let your heart dance!
Let's get it up, get it up, get it up
指を鳴らせば変わる景色が
If you snap your fingers, the scenery changes.
いくつになっても ほら Roleplay
No matter how old you get, look, it's a roleplay.
今宵の主役は私よ
Tonight, the star of the show is me!
One, two, let's go, 3, 4!
It's my showtime!
Let the show begin! 最高潮のショー
Let the show begin! This ultimate show...
楽しんでみまショー
...let's sit back and enjoy the show!
一度きりの人生だもん
After all, it's a once-in-a-lifetime life,
Darling darling darling yeah
恋も仕事も一切合切
Love, work, and absolutely everything,
楽しむのよ
I'm going to fully enjoy it!
1, 2, 3, 4!
Let the show begin...
照らすムーンライト スポットライトにして
Turning the shining moonlight into my spotlight.
Let's get it up, get it up, get it up
踊りだす足元
My feet starting to dance
軽快なステップで
with light and nimble steps.
Let's get it up, get it up, get it up
音を鳴らせば
If you make a sound,
拍手喝采が届く
thunderous applause will reach us...
スタンディングオベーション
...with a standing ovation.
今宵の主役にあなたも
You, too, are the star tonight!
One, two, let's go, 3, 4!
It's our showtime!
Let the show begin! 最高潮のショー
Let the show begin! This ultimate show...
楽しんでみまショー
...let's sit back and enjoy the show!
一度きりの人生だもん
After all, it's a once-in-a-lifetime life,
Darling darling darling yeah
恋も仕事も一切合切
Love, work, and absolutely everything,
楽しむのよ
I'm going to fully enjoy it!
1, 2, 3, 4!
Let the show begin...
Ahahaha! Come on, trombone!
Oh, oh, oh!
Yeah!
Oh, oh, oh, wow!
Do you love me? Everybody, go crazy for me, yeah!
Please dance till the last
Please dance till the very last
今にも
even right now...
Let's do it! Ready, ready, ready, ready...
So beautiful
何度も
No matter how many times
立ち上がろう
Let's rise up again
Let's go, we're ready, ready, ready, ready!
Let the show begin あなたも 燃え尽きましょう
Let the show begin, you too, let's burn ourselves out!
一度きりの人生でしょ Darling, Darling, Darling, yeah
It's a once-in-a-lifetime life, right? Darling, Darling, Darling, yeah!
恋も 仕事も いいだしっぺの勝ちよ
In love and work, the one who takes the initiative wins!
1, 2, 3, 4, hop!
Let the show begin
Let the show begin 最高潮 楽しんじゃいましょう
Let the show begin! Let's have fun at the absolute climax!
一度きりの人生なんだ Darling, Darling, Darling, yeah
It's a once-in-a-lifetime life, Darling, Darling, Darling, yeah!
恋も 仕事も いいだしっぺの勝ちよ
In love and work, the one who takes the initiative wins!
1, 2, 3, 4, hop!
This is my showtime!
I'm breaking... 他の誰でもないの、Me
I'm breaking... I'm like nobody else, just Me
君の願いも簡単に叶えたいから、Look at me
Because I easily want to grant your wishes, Look at me
Ladies, get up, stand up, 嘘だらけの世界とは break up
Ladies, get up, stand up, breaking up with this world full of lies
I wish no filter, ありのままで描いてく future
I wish, with no filter, painting the future just as it is
みんな誤魔化し ありのままの I don't need a lie
Everyone is deceiving, but as I am, I don't need a lie
理不尽だとも 間違わない I don't need to cry
Even if it's unreasonable, I won't make mistakes, I don't need to cry
こだわる My style 幾度の波 超えてく My life, right now
Obsessing over My style, overcoming waves, my life right now
Judge to my life 見せるだけ 振り向かない
Judge my life, I'll just show you, I won't look back
魅せつけるの Luxury
Fascinating you with luxury
満たして、満たして、吐き出すの My world
Fill it up, fill it up, and vomit out my world
見せつける Ecstasy
Showing you ecstasy
Don't replay, I don't care, だから Go my way
Don't replay, I don't care, so Go my way
Show me without the filter
Be naked
望むままに get it
Get it exactly as you wish
Be red
Show me without the filter
Do you understand?
We are red, We must say, 望むままに get it
We are red, We must say, get it exactly as you wish
脳裏も揺らす 揺らしてみせる
Shaking your mind, I'll show you I can shake it
We are red, あの手、だから 遠慮はしない
We are red, because of that trick, so I won't hold back
手がつけられない反動、走るから乱暴
An uncontrollable reaction, running wildly
惑わせる Fantasy
Deceiving fantasy
満たしても 騙されはしないの
Even if filled, I won't be fooled
幕開ける Finally
It finally begins
I okay, I'm okay, だから Don't mistake
I'm okay, I'm okay, so Don't mistake
Show me without the filter
Be naked
望むままに get it
Get it exactly as you wish
Be red
Show me without the filter
自分隠すの、もう楽だよね
Hiding yourself is much easier, isn't it?
周りに合わせていれば、それで
If you just go along with everyone, with that...
とりあえず一人にならずに済むから バイバイなの？
Since it means at least you won't end up alone, is it "bye-bye"?
正体はもう気付いて 目は合わせ 謎にうずいてる
Realize its true form already, eyes locked, throbbing mysteriously
なのになんで諦めてる、もう一度確かめて
So why are you giving up? Check once more
始めましょう、リアルなショー、どこからでも、好きにどうぞ
Let's begin the real show, from wherever you like, please go ahead
愛を放ちに Show me without the filter
To release love, show me without the filter
Hey, what you want? Tell me, please, don't be shy.
Hey, what you need? 大大丈夫さ
Hey, what you need? It's okay
Hey, what you want? Tell me, please, don't be shy.
そのままで Get it on, Yeah, it's cool.
Just as you are, Get it on, Yeah, it's cool.
Hey, what you want? Tell me, please, don't be shy.
Hey, what you need? 大丈夫さ
Hey, what you need? It's okay
Hey, what you want? Tell me, please, don't be shy.
そのままで Get it on, Yeah, it's cool.
Just as you are, Get it on, Yeah, it's cool.
ユルサナイ
I won't forgive you
ずっとしたが顔が可愛いな
Your submissive face is always so cute.
君のその身体が欲しいの
I want that body of yours.
Luv me, Naughty, Luv me, Luv me, Hearty, Hearty
かわいそうね君は 悪い子なの？どう？
How pitiful, are you a bad kid? How about it?
どの子がお好きで サニサニ
Which child do you like, sunny, sunny?
色目やお上手で たばかり
Flirting so well, tricking me.
君に躍らされちゃって 私は狂う
Danced around by you, I go mad.
What is Lavy?
君のなかみまで 骨の髄まで
To your inside, to the marrow of your bones.
入れたてなら 後になる 愛のパペット
If freshly put in, it becomes a puppet of love later.
胸が苦しいね 息が詰まるのね
My chest is tight, my breath is suffocated, right?
それが恋と教えてあげる アハハ
Let me teach you that that is love, ahaha.
ずるの底で ほら囁いて
At the bottom of cheating, look, whisper to me.
いい子ね 首輪はつけた？君はラヴィ
Good boy, did you put on the collar? You are Lavy.
イカれちゃったのね 恋は盲目ね
You've gone crazy, haven't you? Love is blind.
したいようでしてあげるわ イッツアハハ
As you wish, I will do it for you, it's ahaha.
濡れた君の赤い 痕跡 溺れるまで
Until drowning in your wet red traces.
痛いの飛んでいけ 死んで媚びるまで
Pain, pain, fly away, until you die and flatter me.
愚かね 愚かね 間抜けな顔して 君は悪い子なの？
How foolish, how foolish, making a dumb face, are you a bad child?
痛いのがお好きで サニサニ
You like pain, sunny, sunny.
洗うお口はチャックで何何？
Wash your mouth, zip it up, what, what?
ねぇ 躍らされちゃう 君も狂う
Hey, you get danced around, you go mad too.
What is Lavy?
君のなかみまで 骨の髄まで
To your inside, to the marrow of your bones.
しゃぶり尽くせば もう空っぽのパペット
If sucked dry, it's already an empty puppet.
胸が苦しいね 息が詰まるのね
My chest is tight, my breath is suffocated, right?
それが恋と教えてあげる アハハ
Let me teach you that that is love, ahaha.
君はピエロね 愛を囁いて
You are a clown, whispering love.
人間の形した 君はラヴィ
In human form, you are Lavy.
イカれちゃったのね 恋は盲目ね
You've gone crazy, haven't you? Love is blind.
したいようでしてあげるわ イッツアハハ
As you wish, I will do it for you, it's ahaha.
報い償う 穢れた血に溺れるまで
Until paying the penalty and drowning in defiled blood.
痛いの飛んでいけ 息が止まるまで
Pain, pain, fly away, until your breath stops.
報い償う 穢れた血に溺れるまで
Until paying the penalty and drowning in defiled blood.
痛いの飛んでいけ 息が止まるまで
Pain, pain, fly away, until your breath stops.
みんなー！
Everyone!
本日は！
Today!
伊咲リオナ生誕祭2026に遊びに来てくれて、本当にありがとうございます！
Thank you so much for coming to play at Isaki Riona's Birthday Festival 2026!
Let the show begin!
えーっと、『Bivi』、『きゅうくらりん』、
Um, "Bivi," "Kyu-kurarin,"
『ラヴィ』と3曲続けて披露させていただきました！
and "Lavy," I performed three songs in a row!
どうですかー？
How was it?
改めて自己紹介をさせてください。
Let me introduce myself again.
私の元に、おいで。
Come to me.
リオナインダステージ！
Riona in the stage!
MAHOGRAのリーダー、伊咲リオナです。ぷらぷらー！よろしくお願いします！
The leader of MAHOGRA, Isaki Riona. Pura-pura! Nice to meet you!
はあ、息切れる。息切れる、息切れるんですけど、
Whew, I'm out of breath. I'm so out of breath, but...
はい、今日のですね、ハッシュタグはこちら！
Yes, today's hashtag is right here!
#伊咲リオナ生誕祭2026 です！
It's #IsakiRionaBirthdayFestival2026!
たくさん、たくさん、呟いてください！
Please tweet lots and lots!
私絶対見に行くのでね！
I'll definitely go check them!
みんなが感想とか送ってくれるの、すごく楽しみにしています。
I'm really looking forward to seeing everyone's thoughts and comments.
そしてですね、本日
And also, today,
ライブパフォーマンスさせていただくステージはこちらです！どうですか？
the stage where I will be performing live is right here! What do you think?
ショーみたいでさ、めっちゃ良くない？
It looks like a show, isn't it awesome?
あとね、伊咲リオナっていうね、名前がたくさん刻まれていたり、ハートの風船だったり、王冠だったり、
Also, my name, Isaki Riona, is engraved all over, along with heart balloons and crowns,
いろんな装飾があって、とってもキラキラしてます！
there are so many decorations, making it super sparkly!
ここでね、踊れることが今日すごく、すごく幸せです。ありがとうございます。
I'm so, so happy to be able to dance here today. Thank you so much.
そして、本日のライブのタイトルが「The One and Only」となっております。
And the title of today's live is "The One and Only."
こちらの意味は、唯一無二という意味です。
This means unique and irreplaceable.
このタイトルに恥じないように、全力で、全力でパフォーマンスしていくので、
To live up to this title, I'll perform with all my might,
どうかこの時間が、あなたの心に何か届けられる、そんな時間になれるように、
so I hope this time can deliver something to your heart.
今日は頑張りたいと思います！
I'll do my best today!
それでは、次はお待ちかねのゲストパートです！
Now, next is the guest segment you've all been waiting for!
どうぞ！
Here you go!
Blah virtual blah blah blah blah... I'm a v.
Blah virtual blah blah blah... I'm a v.
Blah virtual blah blah blah blah... I'm a vだ la vida な diva. Love that blah blah blah.
Blah virtual blah blah blah... I'm a V, la vida a diva. Love that blah blah blah.
たかだか生裸の魂魄
Only raw soul confusion.
さわらば可愛いの混沌
Once touched, it's a cute chaos.
高天ヶ原からほら 「堕としてあげる」
Look, from Takamagahara, "I'll let you fall."
Hi, そうメンヘラでも面がキュートならメンキラー
Hi, even if mental, if the face is cute, a men-killer.
とか貼られたレッテル 逝ってるメンタルは
Labels like that are pasted, but my mental state is dead.
最強スマイルで 転がしてけファンダム
Roll with the fandom with the strongest smile.
誤魔化してる傷心性根 晒されたら引退 にゃんてな
Disguising my hurt disposition, if exposed, it's retirement, just kidding!
I'm a v. I'm a v. I'm a 泡沫よ
I'm a V, I'm a V, I'm just a transient bubble.
I am la vida な diva 淫らは嫌よ
I am la vida, a diva, I hate being lewd.
夢見てる少年A
Dreaming boy A.
夢見てる少女A
Dreaming girl A.
vならvidaは甘々甘々？ No!
If you are V, is life super sweet? No!
ちょん切る我利我利妄想 笑わせんな我がセンター
Cut off the selfish delusions, don't make me laugh, I'm the center.
センター
Center
誰よりも客寄せるパンダー
A crowd-pleasing panda like no other
我らは何だ？ まるで生んだ
What are we? It's like we're born...
自己愛性勝者
...self-loving winners.
Am I V?
甘い 甘い
Sweet, sweet
アライ アライ
Allies, allies
さらに
Furthermore,
お終いに So Love Me.
in the end, so love me.
お出まし平民モンスター
Here comes the plebeian monster!
My name is Love Love
愛でられたら墓までラフだ
If loved, I'll be laughing all the way to the grave.
Am I bitter? All about that
心の中は Smooth like butter
Inside my heart is smooth like butter.
Touch me したいならほらエンター
If you want to touch me, come on, press enter.
Catch me でハイピース
Catch me and high peace!
召し上がるシチュはわからないけど Wow
I don't know the situation of consuming, but wow,
割れ心叫ぶ一つも Lifer
my broken heart screams, not even one lifer.
生きる姿や魂を今
The way we live and our souls, right now,
二つにして愛をバラバラに
split them in two, scattering love to pieces.
生まれた時の喜びは没収
The joy of being born is confiscated,
最期にさよならでいいな
is a final goodbye really okay?
ダメね
No good, is it?
Wacha Wacha
WachaはMecha Mecha?
Is Wacha Mecha Mecha?
Wacha Wacha
WachaはMecha Mecha?
Is Wacha Mecha Mecha?
楽観な廊下ね ららら交換で交換ね
Optimistic hallway, swapping with a la-la-la,
形骸な正体ね あら
a hollow true form, oh my!
WachaはMecha Mecha?
Is Wacha Mecha Mecha?
楽観な廊下ね あら
An optimistic hallway, oh my,
あらら感感で共感ね
sympathizing with an oh-my feeling.
一巻の終わりだね
It's the end of the line, isn't it?
あー、めんどな
Ah, what a pain.
I am a VIP, I am a VIP, I am a 泡 泡よ
I am a VIP, I am a VIP, I am bubbles, bubbles,
La Vida I am Diva, 淫らは嫌よ
La Vida I am Diva, I don't want to be lewd!
夢見てる少年
The dreaming boy,
夢見てる少女へ
to the dreaming girl...
VIPならVIPは 甘々甘々 No!
If you're a VIP, VIP is sweet, sweet, sweet, sweet, no!
そうよ、うざい
That's right, annoying.
子供の頃言われたもんだ
I was told when I was a kid,
あのヒーローショーの人形の背中には チャックは付いてないから開くな
that the hero show doll doesn't have a zipper on its back, so don't open it!
バーチャルだヒューマンだ 死のごの言うな
Virtual this, human that, don't fuss over details!
存在はワンワンダ
Existence is a one-wonder.
荒れても惚れても死のごのバラバラな
Even if wild or in love, scattering to pieces!
Virtual Blah Blah, Virtual Blah Blah
Virtual Blah Blah, Virtual Blah Blah, Blah Blah Blah!
Ah, and, Virtual Blah Blah
Are you ready for...
惚れたら死ぬぞ
If you fall in love, you'll die!
Virtual Blah Blah, Virtual Blah Blah
Virtual Blah Blah
Um, I am a V
それじゃあ、先輩！
Alright, Senpai!
はい、来てくれてありがとうございました！
Thank you so much for coming!
こちらこそありがとうございました！
No, thank you so much!
一緒に踊れて嬉しかったです！
I was so happy to dance with you!
ねー！
Right?!
そらりおー！
Sorario!
そらりおは不滅です！
Sorario is eternal!
バイバイー！
Bye-bye!
Yeah, that's karma, yeah, get down
Ah-ooh
Checkmate, I'm a superstar. Stay insane, but you rock with it, ah
Yeah, like 24/7 I'm a hot mess, ya love-hate
Get less boring, oh my god!
ホームラン バタバタ swing my shot, whoop-whoop, uh yeah
Home run, batabata, swing my shot, whoop-whoop, uh yeah,
Like a villainous villainess, bring home the jackpot
勇者も悪役も変わらない
The hero and the villain are no different.
派手にブチかまそう
Let's blow things up in style!
Ya, ya, ya, ya
Life's just a tightrope, why not stop to fool around?
Chaotic good is peak right now, I can show ya how
Ya, ya, ya, ya
Don't get confused, we are not the same
I'm a ruthless dame
No way, no way-ya, way-ya, way-ya
Good vs evil is so overdone
Let's all kick back and party, just leave it to moi
Whoops, whoops, ah!
Loosen my lips, loosen my li-li-lips, yeah
Ah, that's karma, ta-da, hahaha
Whoops, whoops, ah!
Loosen my lips, I'm about to say some-ish get it?
Yeah, that's karma ta-da, hahaha
Sorry, I'm just better
Sorry, we're go-getters
Ain't my fault we're wicked, stunning, tricky
Why you running? (Oh)
Betcha think you're clever
Whatever!
Ah, talk about a kumbaya
Ya, ya, ya, ya
Hey yo, check this out
フルボッコンボっちゃって
Beating them up completely,
欲望召し上がれ
feast on your desires.
アイ ハート get down ウィンク
see yonara サイコですわ
I, heart, get down, wink, goodbye, it's psycho.
ドメスティック
Domestic,
ドラマティック
Dramatic,
愛しき人々 この指とまれ
my beloved people, gather 'round!
Ayy, yo
ハードに ハートは ハイになって弾けて
Our hearts go hard, getting high and bursting,
恥じらい捨てちゃえ 叫び踊り誇れ
throw away your shyness, scream and dance with pride!
激動的 show 体 酔いしれてちょーだい
Drown yourself in this turbulent show body!
道化のパラダイス 惹かれ合う感覚が
The clown's paradise, the feeling of mutual attraction...
共鳴 共鳴
...resonates, resonates.
Good vs evil, but I'm which one?
Just stuck here in the middle
That's not any fun
What? Ah!
Loosen my lips
Loosen my li-li-lips, yeah
Ah, that's karma
Da-dahahaha!
What? Ah!
Loosen my lips
I'm about to say some ish, get it
Yeah, that's karma
Da-dahahaha!
想像から創造
From imagination to creation
衝動から猛攻
From impulse to onslaught
ほらあっという間に 華麗に変身 変幻自在
Look, in an instant, glamorously transforming, freely changing
ドクドク心拍
My heart's pounding...
フライハイハッ
Fly high, hah!
ハッハッハッ
Hah hah hah!
Sorry, I'm just better
Sorry, we're go-getters
Ain't my fault we're wicked, stunning, tricky / Why you running?
Bet'cha think you're clever
Whatever!
Yeah, yeah, yeah
Talk about a "kumbaya"
Isekai queen, switch tuning minor
カラフルに カコフォニー
Colorful cacophony
Why, yeah, yeah, yeah
If it's today... hachamecha
Welcome to Miss Fortune's game
Yeah, yeah, yeah
カリオペ先輩、来てくれてありがとうございました！
Calliope-senpai, thank you so much for coming!
イェーイ！楽しかった！また歌いましょう！
Yeah! That was fun! Let's sing together again!
はい、また歌いましょう！
Yes, let's sing together again!
また歌いましょう！
Let's sing together again!
歌いましょう！
Let's sing!
チュチュチュ！
Chu chu chu!
カルテNo.2222
[Karte No. 2222]
あー...♡
Ah...♡
2-2-2-2 (Kyu kyu kyu)
2-2-2-2 (Doom doom doom)
2-2-2-2 (Kyu kyu kyu kyuru)
2-2-2-2
2-2-2-2 (Kyu kyu kyu)
2-2-2-2 (Burn burn burn)
Chu chu chu
Open your Karte♡
救助不可能 (Darling)
Rescue impossible (Darling)
恋の病なの (Dirty)
It's love sickness (Dirty)
どんどん熱を上げていく Virus (Love me)
The virus that raises the heat steadily (Love me)
危険な魔法 (Twinkle)
Dangerous magic (Twinkle)
試してみる？ (Blink)
Wanna try it? (Blink)
飽くまで天使の優等生 (Heaven in hell)
The honors student who is an angel until the end (Heaven in hell)
ドキドキ
Doki doki
動機は純粋 甘い
The motivation is pure, sweet
曖昧乙女心
ambiguous maiden heart
どっちどっち
Which way, which way?
さあ 手の平の迷宮へようこそ
Welcome to the labyrinth on the palm of your hand
「いい子だね♡」
"You're a good girl♡"
カルテNo.
Karte No.
運命の2222
Fated 2222
鳴り止まないサイレン音が
The siren that won't stop ringing is
Wee woo woo
好き？好き？早まる愛の心電図
The heart rate monitor of love that is accelerating
はい お薬をどうぞ
Here is your medicine
To to to you
2-2-2-2 (Kyu kyu kyu kyuru)
2-2-2-2 (Doom doom doom doom)
2-2-2-2 (Zoom zoom zoom zoom)
2-2-2-2
2-2-2-2 (Kyu kyu)
2-2-2-2 (Burn burn burn)
Chu chu chu
Open your Karte♡
二十四時間 (During)
24 hours (During)
呼吸困難 (Dizzy)
Respiratory distress (Dizzy)
真っ赤な薔薇のトゲにキスして (Kiss me)
Kiss the thorns of the bright red rose (Kiss me)
麻酔みたいな台詞 (Drinking)
Lines that sound like anesthesia (Drinking)
魔性のBabyface (Labyrinth)
The devil's babyface (Labyrinth)
籠で飛び交う青い鳥 (Try & Error)
The blue bird that flies in the cage (Try & Error)
ドクドク
Dokudoku
毒みたいな支配笑顔に
Like a poisonous, controlling smile
落下寸前
Just before falling
チクタク
Tick-tock
もう時間がない 秘密の正体
There's no more time, the secret's true identity
「悪い子かも♡」
"Maybe I'm a bad girl♡"
カルテNo.
Karte No.
運命の2222
Fated 2222
追いつけない
Can't catch up
超スピードで
At super speed
好き？好き？乱れる愛の心電図
Do you like it? Do you like it? The disordered heart rate monitor of love
もう重症みたいです...
Looks like I'm already critically ill...
Too too too too me
先生！緊急事態です！
Doctor! It's an emergency!
カルテNo.2222の患者様です！
It's the patient from Karte No. 2222!
見てください！心電図がハートの形になってます！
Look! The electrocardiogram is in the shape of a heart!
もしもし、聞こえますか？
Hello, can you hear me?
もっと好きになっちゃう注射しましょうね！
Let's give you an injection to make you love me more!
大丈夫ですよ、ずっと私が手当てしていますからね。
It's okay, I'll be treating you the whole time.
心拍数がどんどん上がっています！
The heart rate is rising rapidly!
あ、私の声聞こえますかー？
Ah, can you hear my voice?
好きなところ言えますかー？
Can you tell me what you like about me?
あーあ、だから言ったのに。
Ah, see, I told you so.
カルテNo.
Karte No.
さあ 選んで 4 Card
Now, choose a 4-of-a-kind
裏表ツインテールの Joker
The double-sided twin-tailed Joker
Time over そう神様さえ言う通り
Time's over, just as even God says
You're falling
ぎゅっと結んだリボン 誓いましょうティンドン
Let's tie the ribbon tight and make a vow, ding-dong
運命の警告が連なる暗示
A hint of consecutive warnings of fate
2-2-2
カルテ
Karte
No.
運命の2222
Fated 2222
鳴り止まないサイレン音が
The siren that won't stop ringing is
Wee woo woo woo
好き？好き？早まる愛の心電図
The heart rate monitor of love that is accelerating
はい お薬をどうぞ
Here is your medicine
To to to you
2-2-2-2 (Kyu kyu kyu kyuru)
2-2-2-2 (Doom doom doom doom)
2-2-2-2 (Zoom zoom zoom zoom)
2-2-2-2
2-2-2-2 (Kyu kyu)
2-2-2-2 (Burn burn burn)
Chu chu chu
Open your Karte♡
見上げて
Looking up at...
あの夜空に
...that night sky,
浮かぶ星たち
...the stars floating there...
ふっと 君の声が
Suddenly, your voice...
あの頃輝いてたかな
was it shining back then?
今になっては
Now that it's over,
ずっとわからないまま
I still don't understand it at all.
オーケストラ
[Orchestra]
あの時
Back then...
君がついた嘘
...the lie you told,
問いただせずに泣いたあの坂道
on that hill where I cried, unable to ask you about it.
この先 君と会えないの？
Will I never see you again from now on?
離ればなれに身を任せていた
I just let myself go along with us drifting apart.
いつもの防波堤が
The breakwater we always went to...
風に消えてく
...is fading into the wind.
誰にも見せない
That figure of yours...
その姿を
...which you show to no one.
もうちょっとだけ見てたかったんだ
I wanted to look at it for just a little longer.
時がそっと睨んでいる
Time is quietly glaring at us.
その手と手繋いで
Holding those hands together,
笑いあった声は忘れはしないよ
I will never forget the sound of us laughing.
こんなにも流してた涙も
Even the tears we shed so much,
交わす声もオーケストラ
and the voices we exchanged, form an orchestra.
やがて訪れたよね
Eventually, it came, didn't it?
さよならの声 忘れはしないよ
I will never forget the voice saying goodbye.
あんなにも近くにいたはずが
We were supposed to be so close,
今では繋がりなんてあの空だけ
but now, our only connection is that sky.
Wow...
下らない
Let's have...
話をしよ
...some silly talks.
馬鹿らしくなって投げたごちそう
The feast we threw away after it felt ridiculous.
この先君と何年も
From now on, for many years with you...
時の流れに身を任せても
...even if I entrust myself to the passage of time.
いつもの冗談が街に消えてく
The usual jokes are fading into the town.
誰にも見せない僕の姿を
This figure of mine that I show to no one.
もうちょっとだけ見せたかったんだ
I wanted to show you for just a little longer.
時がそっと睨んでいる
Time is quietly glaring at us.
この目と目合わせて
Locking our eyes like this,
はっきりとしたい もう出来ないかな
I want to make it clear, but maybe I can't anymore?
こんなにも融かし合って繋いだ手が
Our hands, which held and melted together so much...
音立てるオーケストラ
...form an orchestra that makes noise.
ここで何をしてるの？
What are you doing here?
わからないのは僕のせいなんだね
It's my fault that I don't understand, isn't it?
永遠にこんな日が続くなんて
Believing that days like this would last forever...
神様いたずらなら 戻りたいくらい
If it's a prank of God, I wish I could go back.
その手と手繋いで
Holding those hands together,
笑いあった声は忘れはしないよ
I will never forget the sound of us laughing.
こんなにも流してた涙も
Even the tears we shed so much,
交わす声もオーケストラ
and the voices we exchanged, form an orchestra.
やがて訪れたよね
Eventually, it came, didn't it?
さよならの声 忘れはしないよ
I will never forget the voice saying goodbye.
忘れはしないよ
I will never forget you.
あんなにも近くにいたはずが
We used to be so close, but...
今では繋がりなんて
now, our only connection is...
この空だけ
...this sky.
せーの！
Ready, set...
リオナ、お誕生日おめでとう！
Happy Birthday, Riona!
ありがとう！
Thank you!
なんと！FGのみんなが来てくれました！ありがとう！
Wow! Everyone from FG came! Thank you!
やったー！おめでとう！
Yay! Congratulations!
ついにね、初めての生誕ライブで。そしてFGでこうやってライブできて、凄く嬉しいよ！
Finally, my first birthday live! And being able to perform with FG like this, I'm so happy!
祝わせてくれてありがとう！
Thank you for letting us celebrate!
エモかったね / エモかった？ / エモかった！本当に！
That was emotional. / Emotional? / Emotional! Really!
え、どうですか？エモかったですか？
Well, how was it? Was it emotional?
泣いちゃったよ、リオナちゃん！ / 泣いちゃった、泣いちゃった！
You cried, Riona-chan! / You cried, you cried!
泣いちゃった！大成功だよ！
She cried! It's a huge success!
みんなとこうやってね、みんなの誕生日ライブがあるかどうかはわかんないんだけど...
Perform like this together... Though I don't know if everyone will have their own birthday live...
リーダーの特権だからね。リーダーにしか無いよ
It's a leader's privilege. Only leaders get one.
えー！私達も察してよ！どういうこと？！あるかもしれないじゃん！
What?! Guess how we feel too! / What do you mean?! / There might be!
リーダー、出させてくれてありがとうございました！ / 本当に！
Leader, thank you for letting us perform! / Really!
リーダーとしての威厳を保ちつつ、
While maintaining my dignity as a leader...
今日は、誕生日プレゼントに、みんなからの、超絶可愛い「おめでとう！リオナ、おめでとう！」っていうプレゼントが欲しいんだけど、いいかな？
I want a super-cute "Congratulations! Happy Birthday, Riona!" from everyone as a birthday present, is that okay?
嫌です！ / 誕生日なのに？ / ありがとうございましたー！
No way! / Even though it's my birthday? / Thank you very much!
じゃあお祝いしよう！ / 「おめでとう！」みたいなやつ？
Then let's celebrate! / Something like "Congratulations"?
え、じゃあ「せーの」って言うから「リオナおめでとう」って言ってね。オッケー？プレゼントね、プレゼント！
Okay, I'll say "Ready, set..." so say "Happy Birthday, Riona", okay? It's a present!
プレゼントならしょうがないか。ちゃんと可愛くやれよ！可愛くだからね！そうだよ！まあまあ任せてって！可愛くだよね？
If it's a present, I guess we have to. / Do it cutely! / Really cutely, okay? / Leave it to us!
せーの！
Ready, set...
リオナ... おめでとう... / ちょっと待って！男声いる！男声！ダメ！
Riona... Happy Birthday... / Wait! There are manly voices! No!
でもちょっと、見本見せてよ。そうそう、初めての生誕ライブだし
But wait, show us an example. / Yeah, it's your first birthday live.
お祝いの言葉みたいな... / 愛の言葉！ / 愛がいい！ / セクシーで可愛くて愛！ / 全身で！ / リオナさんの愛の言葉まで、3...
Give us a congratulatory message... / Words of love! / Sexy, cute, and full of love! / With your whole body! / Riona-san's words of love in 3...
2... 1... はい！
2... 1... Go!
今年も、来年も、再来年も、あなたに祝ってもらえますように！
I hope you'll celebrate with me this year, next year, and the year after next!
ありがとう！ / あなたへの、お祈りです。
Thank you! / That's my prayer for you.
まるでこの世界で 二人だけみたいだね
It's as if it's just the two of us in this world, isn't it?
なんて少しだけ夢を見てしまっただけ
I just had a little dream like that
つま先に月明かり 花束の香り 指に触れる指
Moonlight on my toes, the scent of a bouquet, a finger touching a finger
さよなら もう行かなきゃ なにもかも忘れて
Goodbye, I must go, forgetting everything...
ガラスの上を 裸足のまま歩く 痛むごとに血が流れて落ちていく
Walking barefoot on the glass, with every stab of pain, blood flows and falls
お願い その赤い足跡を辿って会いに来て
Please, follow those red footprints and come see me
錆びたプールに放たれてく金魚
Goldfish released into a rusty pool,
靴箱の中隠したリンゴ
an apple hidden inside the shoe locker,
しなびた君の肌に残る傷跡
scars left on your withered skin...
波のように泳いだ迷い子
A lost child swimming like waves
どこにいる？ (どこにいるよ)
Where are you? (I'm right here)
何をしてる？ (ずっと見てるよ)
What are you doing? (I'm always watching you)
呼び間違えてみせる
I'll pretend to call you by the wrong name
そばにいてよ 遊びに行こうよ
Stay by my side, let's go play
どこを見るの？
Where are you looking?
ガラスの上 私立ち止まる
I stand still on top of glass
痛むことに血が流れて落ちていく
My blood flows and drips as it hurts
お願い その可愛い足跡をたどって
Please, follow those cute footprints
会いに来て
And come see me
丸いこの世界で二人だけみたいだね
It's like it's just the two of us in this round world
なんて少しだけ夢を見てしまっただけ
That was just a little dream I had
頬を刺す 朝の山手通り
Yamate street in the morning stings my cheeks
煙草の空き箱を捨てる
I throw away an empty box of cigarettes
今日もまた足の踏み場は無い
Today again I have no space even for my feet
小部屋が孤独を甘やかす
And my small room pampers my loneliness
「不穏な悲鳴を愛さないで
"Don't love my unsettled screams,
未来等見ないで
don't look to the future.
確信出来る現在だけ重ねて
Live only in the present you can be confident in.
あたしの名前をちゃんと呼んで
Call out my name right,
身体を触って
touch my body,
必要なのは是だけ認めて」
acknowledge that this is the only thing you need."
愛している 独り泣き喚いて
I love you. I'm bawling alone
夜道を弄れど虚しい
And I wander about the streets at night, but I feel so lifeless
改札の安蛍光灯は
The cheap fluorescent lights at the ticket gates
貴方の影すら落とさない
Don't even cast your shadow
Ah 歪んだ無常の遠き日も
Ah, the warped, uncertain, distant days
セヴンスターの香り
Smell of Seven Stars
味わう如く季節を呼び起こす
And savoring them evoke that season
あたしが望んだこと自体
The very fact that I expected something
矛盾を優に超えて
Goes well beyond contradiction
一番愛しいあなたの声迄
Your voice is the most dearest of all to me
掠れさせて居たのだろう
But did I even make that hoarse?
静寂を...
The silence...
...静寂を破る
...breaking the silence,
ドイツ車と
the German cars and
パトカー
police cars.
サイレン
Sirens,
爆音
the roar of explosions,
現実界
the physical world,
或る浮遊
a certain state of suspension.
不穏な悲鳴を愛さないで
Don't love my unsettling screams,
未来など見ないで
don't look to the future.
確信出来る現在だけ重ねて
Just pile up the present we can be sure of.
あたしの名前をちゃんと呼んで
Call my name properly,
身体を触って
touch my body.
必要なのは是だけ認めて
Acknowledge that this is all you need.
不穏な悲鳴を愛さないで
Don't love my unsettling screams.
確信出来る現在だけ重ねて
Just pile up the present we can be sure of.
あたしの名前をちゃんと呼んで
Call my name properly,
身体を触って
touch my body.
必要なのは是だけ認めて
Acknowledge that this is all you need.
頬を刺す朝の山手通り
On Yamate Street in the biting morning air,
煙草の空き箱を捨てる
I throw away an empty cigarette pack.
今日もまた
Today again,
足の踏み場は無い
there is no place to step,
小部屋が孤独を甘やかす
and this tiny room pampers my loneliness.
ねえ、あんたわかっちゃいない
Hey, you don't understand at all!
誰それがお手元の世界に夢中
Everyone is obsessed with the world in their hands,
化け物の飼い方を学んでる
learning how to tame the monster within.
選ばれる為なら舌を売る
Selling their tongues just to be chosen,
裏切られた分だけ墓を掘る
digging graves for every betrayal.
へらへらのおつむがどうにかして
Their foolish, grinning heads are out of order,
うすら寒い言葉ばかりになる
leaving nothing but chilling words.
覚えない顔とバイバイできるなら
If I can say goodbye to faces I don't remember,
阿修羅にだってなれるわ
I can even turn into Asura!
逃げるエスケイプ エスケイプ エスケイプ 仏のまま
Running, escape, escape, escape, while remaining a Buddha,
飛べるステップ ステップ ステップ 仰せのまま
flying, step, step, step, just as commanded.
アンダスタン アンダスタン
Understand? Understand?
どーどー閻魔様さえ喰らって
Calm down, I'll even devour King Yama!
カタストリスティスティスティック 嵐の中
Catastrophic, -phic, -phic, in the middle of the storm,
跳ねるスキップ スキップ スキップ あっそ、への河童
leaping, skip, skip, skip, oh really? It's a piece of cake.
アンダスタン アンダスタン
Understand? Understand?
いっそ骨の髄までしゃぶって
You might as well suck me dry to the very marrow!
ねえ、あんたわかっちゃいない
Hey, you don't understand at all!
日々の染みを木々にくべて暖をとり合う
Burning the stains of daily lives to warm ourselves,
義理を欠いた彼の四肢は散り散りになる
the limbs of the duty-lacking man are torn to pieces.
知りもせずに意味を美意識だと崇める
Without even knowing, they revere meaning as aestheticism,
擬似餌じみた好意に御の字だった
perfectly content with bait-like kindness.
愉快な御託のフルコースに
With a full course of delightful nonsense,
うわべの面をして可愛がった
pampering them with a superficial face.
くだらない僧と踊るくらいなら
If I have to dance with a worthless monk,
悪魔と手繋ぐわ
I'd rather hold hands with the devil!
逃げるエスケイプ エスケイプ エスケイプ 仏のまま
Running, escape, escape, escape, while remaining a Buddha,
飛べるステップ ステップ ステップ 仰せのまま
flying, step, step, step, just as commanded.
アンダスタン アンダスタン
Understand? Understand?
阿鼻地獄の果てまでロックオン
Locked on all the way to the end of Avici Hell!
カタストリスティスティスティック 嵐の中
Catastrophic, -phic, -phic, in the middle of the storm,
跳ねるスキップ スキップ スキップ あっそ、への河童
leaping, skip, skip, skip, oh really? It's a piece of cake.
アンダスタン アンダスタン
Understand? Understand?
あんた寝言はあの世で言って
Save your sleep talk for the afterlife!
逃げるエスケイプ エスケイプ エスケイプ 仏のまま
Running, escape, escape, escape, while remaining a Buddha,
飛べるステップ ステップ ステップ 仰せのまま
flying, step, step, step, just as commanded.
アンダスタン アンダスタン
Understand? Understand?
どーどー閻魔様さえ喰らって
Calm down, I'll even devour King Yama!
カタストリスティスティスティック 嵐の中
Catastrophic, -phic, -phic, in the middle of the storm,
跳ねるスキップ スキップ スキップ あっそ、への河童
leaping, skip, skip, skip, oh really? It's a piece of cake.
アンダスタン アンダスタン
Understand? Understand?
いっそ骨の髄までしゃぶって
You might as well suck me dry to the very marrow!
ねえ、ギャーギャー言っちゃって
Hey, go on and scream and shout!
Hey, stop your whining, kid!
頭を垂れないで
Ahh, raise that coward's head!
ありがとうございます！
Thank you so much!
みんなありがとう！
Thank you, everyone!
はぁー、やばい、ちょっと息切れた。
Haa, oh my, I'm a bit out of breath.
お水飲ませてくださいね。すいませんね。
Let me get a drink of water. Excuse me.
はぁ、うまい。
Haa, that's good.
すいません、ありがとうございます。
Sorry, and thank you.
お待たせしてすいませんね。
Sorry for keeping you waiting.
えーっと、先ほどは
So, just now...
「フェードアウト」と
I performed "Fade Out",
「罪と罰」と「阿修羅ちゃん」をお届けしました！
"Crime and Punishment", and "Ashura-chan"!
どうでしたでしょうか？
How did you like it?
この後も、まだまだライブは続きます！
The live show will still continue after this!
まだ披露してないあんな曲や
Some songs I haven't performed yet,
こんな曲があるかもね！
or maybe songs like this might be there!
なので、チャンネルはそのままで、まだ見ててくれたら嬉しいです！
So, please keep the channel as is and stay tuned!
ここでみんなにお知らせをさせてください。
Now, I have some announcements for everyone.
こちらです！
Here they are!
伊咲リオナ誕生日記念2026のグッズが出ます！やったー！
Isaki Riona Birthday Celebration 2026 goods are coming out! Yay!
では、詳細を見ていきましょう！
Now, let's take a look at the details!
まずはこちらです。
First up, here is this.
「RIONA ON THE ステージタペストリー」！
"RIONA ON THE STAGE Tapestry"!
イラストは今回、みんちゅん先生に
The illustration this time is drawn
描き下ろししていただきました。
by Minchun-sensei!
ライブ中のリオナをテーマに描かれたイラストで、
With the theme of Riona during a live performance,
とっても可愛いイラストになっているので、タペストリーでぜひ堪能してください！
it's a very cute illustration, so please enjoy it on the tapestry!
2つ目はこちら！
The second one is this!
「リオナとお揃いネックレス」！
"Matching Necklace with Riona"!
真ん中には王冠のデザイン、
With a crown design in the middle,
周りには伊咲リオナのロゴが入っていますので、
and Isaki Riona's logo around it,
シンプルになってますのでね、ぜひリオナとお揃いにしてくれたら嬉しいです。
it's simple, so I'd be happy if you wear it to match with Riona.
次はこちら！
Next is this!
「リオナのぬいを入れるポーチ」！
"Pouch to put Riona's Plushie in"!
リオナっぽさ全開のぬいポーチになってます。
It's a plushie pouch fully packed with Riona's style.
ぜひリオナのぬいを、リオナのぬいを入れてくれたら嬉しいなと思います。
I hope you will put Riona's plushie, Riona's plushie inside.
ぬい以外に使っても大丈夫だよ、ポーチになるよ。
It's fine to use for things other than plushies, it works as a pouch too.
そしてそして、最後はこちら！
And, and, the last one is this!
「くしゃみ連発ぬいキーホルダー」！
"Sneeze-Repeatedly Plushie Key Ring"!
今回描き下ろしイラストの衣装のぬいぐるみキーホルダーになってます。
This is a plushie key ring in the outfit of the newly drawn illustration.
なんとね、この手の部分をポチッと押すと、
And if you press this hand part,
「ハクション！」って言うので、
it says "Achoo!",
いっぱい押してね、いっぱい浴びてもらえばと思います。
so please press it a lot to get showered with it, I think!
それでは改めてね、フルセットの方を全部見ていきましょう。
Now, let's take a look at the full set together.
こちら！
Here!
盛りだくさん！
So much stuff!
もちろん、フルセット購入特典もあります。
And of course, there's a bonus for purchasing the full set.
こちら！
Here!
フルセット購入特典の1つ目は、
The first full set purchase bonus is
直筆サインと箔押しメッセージ入りのバックステージパス風カードです！
a backstage pass-style card with a hand-written signature and foil-stamped message!
こちらもみんちゅん先生のイラストに、すべて私がね、
This one also features Minchun-sensei's illustration, and I will...
1つ1つ心を込めてサインさせていただくので、よかったらぜひ買ってみてください！
sign each one with all my heart, so please check it out!
2つ目は特典ボイス！
The second bonus is a special voice track!
「ライブ前に君と。」
"With you before the live show."
ライブ前のね、こう緊張して、はぁーってなってるリオナを励ますシチュエーションとなっております。
It's a scenario where you encourage Riona when she gets nervous before the show.
ぜひボイスの方は聞いてくれると嬉しいです。
I hope you'll listen to the special voice!
こちらのグッズは21時からカートオープンです。
The cart opens for these goods at 21:00.
みんなよかったらぜひぜひゲットしてください！
Everyone, please be sure to get them!
そして、大事なお知らせが
And, I have another important announcement,
2つ目あります！
the second one!
聞いてください。
Please listen.
ドゥルドゥルドゥルドゥル、ドン！
Drumroll... bam!
伊咲リオナの初ソロの新曲が出ます！
Isaki Riona's first solo original song is coming out!
やったー！
Yay!
タイトルは「Ring my name」です。
The title is "Ring my name".
こちら、私の想いだったり、
This song contains my thoughts,
これから先、どうやって進んでいくか、私は進んでいくぞ、
and how I'm going to move forward from now on—that I will keep moving forward!
というのが、オシャレで優雅に、エレガントに表現された曲となっております。
It's expressed in a stylish, graceful, and elegant way.
こちら、セクシーな振り付けもついているので、よかったらそこに注目してくださると嬉しいです。
It also has sexy choreography, so I'd appreciate it if you keep an eye on that.
この後、このライブが終わった後すぐにMVも公開されますし、
The MV will be released right after this live ends,
この後24時からデジタルリリースもあるので、ぜひいっぱい聴いてくれると嬉しいです。
and the digital release starts at 24:00, so please listen to it a lot!
やっぱり、この後は新曲やっちゃいますよね！
And of course, I'm going to perform the new song after this!
ということでね、まあやっていくんですけど、
So, I will perform it, but...
その前にね、ちょっと語らせてくださいよ。
before that, let me talk a little bit.
まあね、リオナはね、まだまだなことがいっぱいあって、
Well, there are still many things that I'm not good enough at,
叶えたい夢もいっぱいあります。
and I have many dreams I want to fulfill.
なので、まだまだ何も手にしてない私かもしれませんが、
So, even though I might have achieved nothing yet,
一緒についてきてくれたあなたと一緒に、
I want to make various dreams and memories
色んな夢だったり、思い出を作っていきたいです。
together with you who followed me here.
絶対に後悔はさせないので、
I will never make you regret it,
これからも私についてきてくれると嬉しいです。よろしくお願いします！
so I'd be happy if you continue to follow me. Thank you!
そして、この後は新曲の披露の前に、
And after this, before performing the new song,
ホロライブの先輩方のオリ曲を使ったダンスメドレーをお届けします！
I will bring you a dance medley using the original songs of my Hololive seniors!
こちら、たくさんのジャンルのダンスを踊る
I'll be dancing to many different genres...
ので、ぜひ見てください！
So please check it out!
行くよ！心の準備できた？
Here we go! Are you ready?
ミュージック、スタート！
Music, start!
あいつもこいつも だ・だ・だ・だ・だ（楽しい！）
This guy and that guy, da-da-da-da-da! (So fun!)
My life is so fucking KAWAII（かわいい！）
My life is so fucking cute! (Cute!)
かわいいね
Cute, isn't she?
R-I-O-N-A, game over, let's get party!
Suck it up, butter cup!
Riona in the house
I'm dressed in lace
甘い嘘は act
Sweet lies are an act
囁くの 「Want more?」
Whispering "want more?"
吐息まで danger
Even my sigh is danger
Every step I take
心ごと奪って
Stealing even your heart
Velvet shadows call my name
微熱は隠して
Hiding a slight fever
午前零時
Midnight
今、Veil が解け
Now, the veil is lifted
I'm breaking into the night
まだ夜は醒めやしない
The night has yet to wake up
さあ、誰も彼も焦がれるままで
Come on, as everyone longs for it
「私を見て」
"Look at me."
Ring my name 響かせるわ
Ring my name, I'll make it resonate
今から watch me rise
From now on watch me rise
Bloom it now 咲き誇れば
Bloom it now, if it blooms and scatters
煌めく Reina
Glittering Reina
指先まで優雅に揺れる
Gracefully swaying even to the fingertips
鏡越しのマリオネット
A marionette through the mirror
壊れそうに微笑んで
Smiling as if it will break
瞳の奥 falling low
Falling low deep in the eyes
唇まで like a ghost
Like a ghost up to the lips
I can't stop
巡る走馬灯
The revolving lantern
さあ、魅せましょう
Come on, let's show it
「堕ちるまで」
"Until I fall"
綺麗な嘘で着飾らない No masquerade
I don't dress up with beautiful lies, no masquerade
Go ahead, skip all cheap romance
それならばいっそ Shall we dance?
Then, rather, shall we dance?
Come say Reina! Reina! Reina!
It's showtime
Flavor, fly, no chaser
今さら Bad, マーク, 連打, Bot, ばっか、やってられねーな
Now, bad, mark, spam, bot, only, I can't take it anymore
I'm a wonder, can't look away, boy
魅せつけるの 全てを賭けて
I'll show it off, betting everything
「Are you ready?」
"Are you ready?"
Click, click, tap, tap, and keep on posing
Flick, flick, snap, snap, and everybody dancing
微熱の中
In the midst of a slight fever,
景色が溶けて
the scenery melts away,
まだ夢は醒めない
the dream has not yet faded.
To younger me, "you're all right"
名もなきあの頃に
Back to those nameless days...
「後悔はない」
"I have no regrets."
Ring my name 響かせるわ
Ring my name, I'll make it ring out.
今からwatch me rise
From now on, watch me rise.
Bloom it now 咲き誇れば
Bloom it now, if I bloom in full glory,
煌めくReina
the shining queen.
明け方まで気高く踊る 琥珀色のマスカレード
Dancing nobly until dawn in an amber masquerade,
壊れそうに舞い乱れ
dancing wildly as if about to break.
Viva la reina
Canta de albaria
Ring my name 響かせるわ
Ring my name, I'll make it ring out.
今からwatch me rise
From now on, watch me rise.
泡沫のティアラに
On a transient tiara,
魅せられ
enchanted...
ただ憧れ
Simply yearning,
手を伸ばして
reaching out my hand.
これからも私についてきてください！
Please continue to follow me!
以上、響咲リオナでした！
That's all from Hibiki Riona!
ありがとうございました！
Thank you very much!